[{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980256623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16566,"timeElapsed":75272},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980264157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7531,"timeElapsed":82806},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980273581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9420,"timeElapsed":92229},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980287612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14029,"timeElapsed":106261},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980292356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4741,"timeElapsed":111005},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980303484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11124,"timeElapsed":122132},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980310059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6572,"timeElapsed":128708},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980337776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":27714,"timeElapsed":156424},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4750,"timeElapsed":161178},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980357121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":13164,"timeElapsed":175770},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":14702,"timeElapsed":190475},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":23157,"timeElapsed":213635},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5940,"timeElapsed":219578},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":8293,"timeElapsed":227874},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4515,"timeElapsed":232393},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":9892,"timeElapsed":242287},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":20847,"timeElapsed":263136},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456766,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":12276,"timeElapsed":275415},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":16887,"timeElapsed":292305},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980485294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":10624,"timeElapsed":303942},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3600,"timeElapsed":307545},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7058,"timeElapsed":314606},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5729,"timeElapsed":320339},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3505,"timeElapsed":323847},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5963,"timeElapsed":329813},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980513804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2637,"timeElapsed":332453},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":9276,"timeElapsed":341731},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"24","question":"Describe your relationship with one or both of your parents.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4646,"timeElapsed":346379},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":11130,"timeElapsed":358573},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3399,"timeElapsed":361975},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":18297,"timeElapsed":380274},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6816,"timeElapsed":387093},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980571311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2864,"timeElapsed":389959},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3382,"timeElapsed":393344},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4240,"timeElapsed":397586},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980600597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":21657,"timeElapsed":419246},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3228,"timeElapsed":422477},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8791,"timeElapsed":432217},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3373,"timeElapsed":435593},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6005,"timeElapsed":441601},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4483,"timeElapsed":446087},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2994,"timeElapsed":449083},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2175,"timeElapsed":451261},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2628,"timeElapsed":453892},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":19397,"timeElapsed":473291},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":5236,"timeElapsed":478530},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":10336,"timeElapsed":489921},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3560,"timeElapsed":493484},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":18028,"timeElapsed":511514},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5163,"timeElapsed":516680},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3625,"timeElapsed":520307},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3729,"timeElapsed":524039},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4313,"timeElapsed":528355},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980718232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":8523,"timeElapsed":536881},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":16719,"timeElapsed":553603},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":9818,"timeElapsed":564307},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":33276,"timeElapsed":597585},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6361,"timeElapsed":603949},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4150,"timeElapsed":608102},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6134,"timeElapsed":614239},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980799769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4177,"timeElapsed":618418},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":6280,"timeElapsed":624701},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":13010,"timeElapsed":637713},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"101","question":"If you could erase one memory from your mind, what would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6815,"timeElapsed":644531},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":11812,"timeElapsed":657350},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":9786,"timeElapsed":667138},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980859720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":11227,"timeElapsed":678369},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980864707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4984,"timeElapsed":683356},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980869145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4434,"timeElapsed":687793},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876738,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7591,"timeElapsed":695387},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3108,"timeElapsed":698497},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980887832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7981,"timeElapsed":706481},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980902457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":14622,"timeElapsed":721106},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":5745,"timeElapsed":726854},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980920302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":11179,"timeElapsed":738951},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980924723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4418,"timeElapsed":743372},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980931986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":7261,"timeElapsed":750635},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980935363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3374,"timeElapsed":754012},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2208,"timeElapsed":756223},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980939517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1940,"timeElapsed":758166},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980943970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4451,"timeElapsed":762619},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980957478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":13506,"timeElapsed":776127},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"140","question":"If you could invent a new flavor of ice cream, what would it be?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4686,"timeElapsed":780816},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980971723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8598,"timeElapsed":790371},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980976864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":5139,"timeElapsed":795513},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980980832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3965,"timeElapsed":799481},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980990064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":9229,"timeElapsed":808712},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980994340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4273,"timeElapsed":812989},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980996939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2596,"timeElapsed":815588},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3504,"timeElapsed":819095},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981006382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5933,"timeElapsed":825030},{"subjectID":"3mla8yx1kx","prolificID":"5eaf365d31f4696340c1841e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b249cef7d19c6581f71a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981011071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4686,"timeElapsed":829720}]